[EP05]
But you
have underestimated me.
Don't worry about my dress.
Fuyuan.
I...
Cuilan.
Let's go.
Change the dress.
Yes.
Amitabha.
What a grand scene.
Sister, you finally came.
I invited you several times, but you refused.
It took the Old Madam to invite you personally
for you to grace us with your presence.
That's quite disrespectful, isn't it?
Madam,
you must be longing
for your granddaughter-in-law.
I think,
how can a niece be as close as a granddaughter-in-law?
Am I right?
Exactly.
It's a custom for a daughter-in-law to greet the elders.
Only our
Young Madam is an exception.
She doesn't follow the rules.
She runs out every other day.
And she didn't greet me when she saw me.
It's the era of transition.
Why is the Ling family so feudal?
Madam,
she didn't mean it.
I heard that
she quarreled with the young marshal
and drank poison.
She must have been unhappy.
that made her late for the greeting.
Sister,
what's bothering you?
Tell us,
maybe I can help.
I only have a brother.
No sister.
How dare you!
Did the Old Madam let you get up?
Fuyuan,
don't move.
Dislocation
is painful.
How dare you!
Fuyuan represents me.
Do you want to rebel?
You're so capricious.
I'll let Xing divorce you now.
Let him divorce me.
Mom,
calm down.
Don't get yourself sick.
Young Madam,
you really
need to change your temper.
Look how you've upset the Old Madam.
Quick,
kneel down
and apologize to the Old Madam properly.
[What's the deal with this Second Concubine?]
Mom,
this granddaughter-in-law
just woke up.
Don't take it seriously.
Don't get yourself sick.
Madam,
her personality
is totally different from before.
But
she survived after being shot.
It's a miracle.
Madam,
don't be mad at her.
Punish me instead.
I'm going to expose the Young Madam.
She's been having an affair with someone.
What?
Cuilan,
what are you talking about?
How could you frame the Young Madam like this?
What a show!
So this is why you called me here.
You're really good at acting.
Miss Ye, you're so eloquent.
You've said all the nice things.
With you around,
that Hu Die
will never
become a movie star.
Sister,
you've really misunderstood me.
Please, Madam, investigate thoroughly.
I saw with my own eyes
Young Madam and that lame man
being intimate during the day.
Ling residence has been kind to me.
I dare not let the Ling family's bloodline be tainted.
It's my fault to see this.
If you don't believe me,
I'm willing to die to prove myself.
This table
can't be damaged
by your strength.
If you want to hit,
hit that pillar.
Use some strength.
Enough, enough.
What's going on here?
But when it comes to reporting,
evidence is indeed crucial.
If everyone were to report by dying like you,
then those servants who signed the death contract with us
would all have to have ulterior motives,
right?
Mom.
Madam,
actually,
Cui Lan has already
about this in private.
But I didn't dare to make a decision,
so I put it off.
That bastard
is outside the yard now.
Now that you know,
why are you still pretending to be a good person?
You...
Let him in.
I'm also curious about what my bastard
looks like.
Bring him here.
That's all?
Would old Su Muwan love such a man?
Your Ladyship,
this man
seems to be
the one who feeds the cat in her yard.
My Lady,
don't you like me the most?
You said
the Young Marshal doesn't know how to cherish you,
I'm the one who cares about you.
We meet every day in Lanxin Garden.
You like me the most.
Kiss your
birthmark on the right waist.
And the mole on your back.
Help me.
Take this
shameless bitch down.
Take this shameless bitch down.
Grandma,
we haven't figured it out yet.
I, Su Muwan,
am deeply in love with Ling Shenxing.
Everyone in the city knows that.
How could I fall in love with such a person?
What do I want from him?
Do I want you
because you have a scar on your face,
or because you are determined despite your disability?
I...
As for you,
I don't know who you took a bribe from
to frame me.
You said I had an affair with you during the day.
Do you have any evidence?
Just based on a birthmark,
a mole,
you want to sentence me to death.
On what basis?
This birthmark
are abnormal growths
during skin development.
Moles
are also a type of...
The arm
is one of the largest exposed parts of the body.
Miss Ye,
I remember you have a mole on your arm too.
Could it be that
I've also had an affair with you?
Madam.
I haven't asked you to speak yet.
Why are you talking?
You said I have a birthmark on my waist.
Okay.
In that case,
Madam,
please have someone examine me.
Mammy,
take the young madam to be examined.
Yes.
Did you check it clearly?
Yes, I did.
I'll report to Madam now.
Su Muwan,
you're good.
You were
so brave just now.
Why are you afraid now?
I'm just worried that you might
put me in prison again.
A butterfly that flies around
is not worth being admired
until it's made into a specimen.
I just want to tell you
I'm not a specimen.
I'm useful to you.
The Young Marshal just feels that his belongings are coveted.
His possessiveness is getting in the way.
I invite Young Master to watch the show.
Kill two birds with one stone.
How about it?
Good.
I'm waiting for this show.
Young Madam does have a birthmark.
Madam.
Cousin.
So,
what Cuilan said is true.
I dare not deceive you.
I saw everything
with my own eyes.
And now, you're here to back me up.
You can see I'm telling the truth.
I'm also telling the truth.
Guards!
Gather the elders of the Ling Family.
Open the ancestral hall.
Drown this
shameless woman in the pond.
Let's see who dares!
Why are you so happy?
You instigated this?
Fuyuan,
teach her the rules.